basunivesh.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy – BasuNivesh

Please read BasuNivesh privacy policy before using blog or submitting any personal information. By using the blog you are accepting the privacy policy of BasuNivesh.

We respect your right to privacy and will protect it when you visit our blog. BasuNivesh has contact information (including e-mail addresses) for specific sections. If you send any correspondence to us, your email address will be used to fulfill your specific requests, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner like adding to our mailing list.

 **Cookies and Tracking Technology**

BasuNivesh may use cookies tracking technology depending on the features offered. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a server and stored in your browser. Cookies can not be used to deliver viruses to your computer and dont run programs. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read any domain of the web server that issued the cookie to you. Cookie and Tracking Technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type, operating system, number of visitors to the site and understanding visitors interest on the site.

Third-party vendors, including Google, also use cookies to serve ads on our site based on a user’s prior visits. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding our privacy policy you may contact us. This privacy policy is reviewed and revised from time to time.
